>> Jem Young: 因此，让我们继续设置我们的注释应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So let's go in to
set up our note application.
我们想做的第一件事就是要改变对 /var/www 的所有权
The first thing we wanna do is we
wanna change ownership of the /var/www
目录。
directory.
所以我们不需要在任何时候都要做一个文件或者修改它。
So we don't have to sudo whenever
we wanna make a file or modify it.
我们只是想用它来做
We just wanna be able
to access it at will.
所以我们要用它的命令
So we're gonna use the chown command.
它是 c-h - own ，更改所有权。
Which is c-h-own, change ownership.
挺有道理的
Kind of makes sense.
-R 表示它是递归的。
The -R means it's recursive.
因此，它将更改 /var www 目录，以拥有下面的所有内容。
So, it's gonna change that /var www
directory to own everything below that.
对不起，我要澄清。
Sorry, I should clarify.
这是您的用户名，实际上不是 $USER。
This is your user name,
not actually $USER.
不等待，该值为 $USER:$USER，抱歉。
Wait no, this one is $USER:$USER, sorry.
[LAUGH] 我将稍后解决此问题，但它是 $USER:$USER。
[LAUGH] I'm gonna fix this later but
it is $USER:$USER.
也可以说正义运动正义运动。
Or you could also say JEM JEM.
这并不重要，但我们正在改变这个目录的所有权。
It doesn't really matter, but we're
changing the ownership of that directory.
所以我现在要做的是确保我的笔记正确无误。
So I'm gonna go to do that now to
make sure I have my notes correct.
很清楚我要说苏多 chown -R
So clear, and I'm gonna say sudo chown -R.
我认为我可以使用 $USER。
I think I can use $USER.
实际上让我看看
Actually, let me just check.
请回传 $USER。
Say, echo $USER.
好的好的
Yes, so that works.
我们可以使用 $USER。 您可以使用实际的命令。
We can use $USER.
You can use your actual command.
>> Jem Young: 但我只会使用 $USER 看起来更酷。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: But
I will use $USER just cuz it looks cooler.
Chown -R $USER:$USER。
Chown -R $USER:$USER.
然后我们说 /var var.
And we say /var var.
>> Jem Young: /www 酷。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: /www cool.
>> Jem Young: 许可权问题可能是蹬性的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: The permissions
thing may seem pedantic.
何必呢
Why bother?
但这意味着，每当您创建文件时，您就不必再执行该文件。
But this means every time you create
a file you don't have to sudo it anymore.
你不是说苏多六
You don't say sudo VI.
您只能说 VI ，因为目录现在归您所有。
You can just say VI because
the directory is now owned by you.
这都是些小东西 [LAUGH ] 。
It's little things [LAUGH].
多年的努力，我学到了，从长远来说，这让它变得容易一点。
Years of doing this I've learned this make
it a little bit easier in the long run.
所以，让我们制作一个应用程序目录。
So let's make an application directory.
因此 mkdir /var/www/app。
So mkdir /var/www/app.
所以 mkdir /www/app，凉爽，
So mkdir /www/app, cool,
我要把它变成这样
and I'm just gonna cd into that.
>> Jem Young: 再一次，你可以随意调用它。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And again,
you're free to call it whatever you want.
你可以称之为 Sweet New Application。
You can call it Sweet New Application.
你可以叫它 Foo
You can call it Foo.
这并不重要，但我只是为了简单的缘故，把它称为应用。
Doesn't really matter, but I'm calling
it app just for simplicity's sake.
> > Jem Young: 然后我会在它上运行 git init ，所以它是init 。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And then I'm gonna
run git init on it, so git init.
我现在就初始化一个空的 git 存储库。
I'm just gonna initialize
an empty git repository for now.
好了到目前为止所有人都来了吗
All right, everybody with me so far?
这可能是 UI 工程师通常来的地方
This is probably the part where
UI engineers generally come in,
其实还有点进一步的
actually a little bit further.
但你喜欢的地方好吧我知道该怎么做
But this the part where you're like,
okay, I know what to do from here.
但这里是所有工作的地方
But getting here is
where all the work's in.
通过这样做，我们就快到了。
And by doing it, we're almost there.
我们几乎是堆的主人
We're almost masters of the stack.
我有时会使用 && 。
I use the &amp;&amp; sometimes.
这就意味着执行此命令，然后执行此命令。
That just means do this command and
then do this command.
这是一种好的链接方式。
It's a good way of chaining things.
我最喜欢做的就是拉它
One of my favorite ones to
do is probably git pull, so
把它从神秘物上拉下来
git pull to pull down from mastery or
whatever.
然后 &&和纱安装因为人们不断更新包
And then &amp;&amp;, and yarn install because
people are constantly updating packages
当我拉一拉的时候它只会在一个命令中完成
when I do a pull and
it just does it all in one command.
没必要 这是个不错的捷径
Not necessary.
It's a nice little shortcut to have.
>> Jem Young: 如果需要，我们可以制作目录。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: We can make
the directories if you want.
我们今天不需要这样做，现在我们可以跳过它了。
We don't have to do that today and,
[SOUND] we can skip it for now.
我们明天就需要它了
We'll need it for tomorrow.
但是，如果需要，您可以创建目录， ui/js ui/html， ui/css。
But if you want, you can make directories,
ui/js ui/html, ui/css.
> > Jem Young: 其实我现在就做，为什么不呢 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Actually,
I'll just do it now, cuz why not?
太好了
So mdir.
>> Jem Young: Ui/js。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Ui/js.
>> Jem Young: 如果您想查看目录以查看其中的内容
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And if you wanna check
a directory to see what's in it without
实际上，你可以说，你可以说，目录名。
actually going in, you can just say ls,
the directory name.
苏瑞告诉我目录在里面
So ls ui tells me
the directory's in there.
>> Jem Young: Nice，现在我们要创建一个空文件。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Nice, so now we're
going to create just an empty file.
我们可以把我的 app.js 保存好
We can save the I app.js which is fine but
如果我们只想创建一个空白文件我们就用这个触摸指令
if we just want to create just a blank
file, we're gonna use the touch command.
触摸只需要修改时间戳记，以防您想
Touch just modifies the time
stamp on it in case you wanna
运行系统的搜索。
run a search of the system.
说，过去一小时我修改过的文件是什么，所以请使用触摸。
Say, what were the files that I modified
in the past hour, so use touch.
不经常使用，但是使用触摸的好处是只能触摸一个文件
Not used that often, but the benefit of
using touch is we can just touch a file
它就会自动产生
and it just creates it automatically.
这就像创建一个空文件的最激烈的方法。
It's like the laziest way
of creating an empty file.
所以我要说的是 app.js
So I'm gonna say touch app.js.
>> Jem Young: 还有 app-js。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And have an app-js.
它比打字快得快多了
It's much faster than typing going VI and
then right quitting saving,
只是有点捷径
just a little shortcut.
接下来我们要做的事很多人都不知道
Next we're gonna do is something that
a lot of people don't know about,
即使我们每天晚上可能使用 npm ，也就是 npm init 命令。
even though we probably use npm
every day is the npm init command.
>> Jem Young: 请参阅 npm init 将设置节点模块。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: See,
npm init will set up your node modules.
它会设置您的包名。
It'll set up your package name.
它会添加许可证。
It'll add a licence.
它会自动为你做所有的事情
It'll do all the stuff for
you automatically.
我要打这个电话应用没问题
So I'm gonna call this, app is fine.
随你说吧
Call it whatever you want.
版本精细，描述，完整堆栈前端或其他内容。
Version fine, description,
full stack front end or something.
>> Jem Young: 入口点，应用程序 js，测试命令，还没有。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Entry point, app-js,
test command, don't have one yet.
Git 存储库，还没有。
Git repository, don't have one yet.
关键词，作者， Jem.
Keywords, author, Jem.
许可证我们说 MIT 不重要
License, let's say MIT, doesn't matter.
看起来好酷
Looks okay, cool.
>> Jem Young: 现在是晚上的晚上，它为我创造了这个容器 .json ，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And now what npm did was
it created this package.json for me,
这很不错
which is nice.
这只是你的支架
It just scaffolds that out for you.
这比手动创造所有这些东西要简单得多。
It's much easier than just manually
creating all these things.
你必须记住语法和所有这些
You have to remember the syntax and
all that.
Npm init 是一个很好的命令。
Npm init is a nice command.
我们现在就安装 Express 。
Let's install Express now.
Express 是基于节点的基于 JavaScript 的 Web 服务器。
Express is a node
JavaScript-based web server.
它是最受欢迎的
It's one of the more popular ones.
我认为它是受欢迎的，但是那里有很多选择。
I think it's waning in popularity,
but there's lots of options there.
有乐乐
There's Happy.
这是 Netflix 发明的
There's the one that Netflix invented.
我不记得它现在叫什么了
I don't remember [LAUGH]
what it's called now.
是我们用的
It's the one we use.
我晚点再查
I'll look it up later.
但最常见的可能是 Express 。
But Express is probably
the most common one.
我试着选择你能轻易地用谷歌搜索的东西
I try to choose things that you can
Google search easily expressing this,
Express 是最容易使用的。
and Express is the easiest one to use.
现在，我们从使用应用程序切换到 npm ，因为我们正在使用节点模块。
So now, we switch from using app to
npm because we're using node modules.
因此， npm i或 npm install express，我们将进行保存。
So, npm i, or npm install express,
and we're gonna save that.
>> Jem Young: Express --保存。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Express --save.
>> Jem Young: Cool，如果我们看看我们的 package.json，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Cool, and
if we check out our package.json,
我们认为它是一种依赖的表达方式
we see it added as a dependency express.
我所犯的一个常见错误是我忘记做了 -- 当我安装我的节点时
A common mistake I make all the time is I
forget to do --save when I install my node
包。
packages.
他们只安装了一次
So they're installed one time and
然后每当我把它拉到另一台电脑的时候
then whenever I pull this repo to
another computer nothing's there.
我想，为什么不工作呢，我忘了保存。
I'm like, why isn't stuff working,
cuz I forgot to save it.
所以别忘了保存
So don't forget to save.
>> Jem Young: 但现在，我们进入更熟悉的领域，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: But now, we're getting
into more familiar territory that we're
就更舒服些了
all a little bit more comfortable in.
因此，让我们编辑 app.js 文件。
So, let's edit that app.js file.
我们要做的就是创建一个骨头表达服务器
And what we're gonna do is we're gonna
create a bare-bones express server.
> > Jem Young: 我们要做的正是我们以前所做的事情，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And it's gonna do
exactly what we were doing before,
简单的 HP 服务器。
that simple HP server.
我本可以使用节点模块 HTTP 构建到节点中。
I could've used the node module HTTP,
which is built into node.
但因为我们使用 Express ，语法略有不同。
But because we're using Express,
the syntax is slightly different.
我们使用 Express cusz 的时间比现在要快得多
We're using Express cuz we can build
on that later a lot faster than
我们可以使用基本的 HTTP 服务器。
we can with a basic HTTP server.
如果你懒不懒
And if you're lazy or not lazy.
我不该这么说
I shouldn't say that.
如果你有手抽筋或是厌倦打字
If you're getting hand cramps or
you just tired of typing,
您可以转至该 URL 并仅复制并粘贴该 URL 。
you can go to this URL and
just copy and paste it.
我会原谅你的
I will forgive you.
>> 演讲者 2: 我想你缺少一个括号。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I think you're
missing a parenthesis.
>> Jem Young: 我缺少括号。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I am missing a parenthesis.
你只复制并粘贴 [LAUGH]。
You just copy and paste [LAUGH].
我会解决的
I'll fix it.
其实我能修吗
Actually can I fix it?
我想这是个截图
I think it's a screenshot.
[ SOUND] 仅复制并粘贴 [LAUGH]。
[SOUND] just copy and paste it [LAUGH].